[{"answer": " Whats up, John?  How was your day", "docId": "05-06", "aSentId": 13, "question": "", "qSentId": 12},{"answer": " Not great.  I had to shell out $450 for health insurance today", "docId": "05-06", "aSentId": 14, "question": " Whats up, John?  How was your day", "qSentId": 13},{"answer": " Really", "docId": "05-06", "aSentId": 15, "question": " Not great.  I had to shell out $450 for health insurance today", "qSentId": 14},{"answer": " Yeah.  As an international student, the school requires it.  I dont understand wh", "docId": "05-06", "aSentId": 16, "question": " Really", "qSentId": 15},{"answer": " Its not like that here.  Hospital expenses, outpatient care, doctors visits, theyr", "docId": "05-06", "aSentId": 20, "question": " Yeah.  As an international student, the school requires it.  I dont understand wh", "qSentId": 19},{"answer": " Are you required by the school to have health insurance", "docId": "05-06", "aSentId": 24, "question": " Its not like that here.  Hospital expenses, outpatient care, doctors visits, theyr", "qSentId": 23},{"answer": " No, American students arent usually required by the school to have a healt", "docId": "05-06", "aSentId": 25, "question": " Are you required by the school to have health insurance", "qSentId": 24},{"answer": " Oh", "docId": "05-06", "aSentId": 29, "question": " No, American students arent usually required by the school to have a healt", "qSentId": 28},{"answer": " So what kind of plan did you get", "docId": "05-06", "aSentId": 33, "question": " Oh", "qSentId": 32},{"answer": " I really have no idea.  I just got this brochure when I paid for it.  I dont reall", "docId": "05-06", "aSentId": 34, "question": " So what kind of plan did you get", "qSentId": 33},{"answer": "Yeah.  Thats the amount that you have to pay out of pocket every year for healt", "docId": "05-06", "aSentId": 39, "question": " I really have no idea.  I just got this brochure when I paid for it.  I dont reall", "qSentId": 38},{"answer": " So I paid all this money for an insurance policy, but I still have to pay more", "docId": "05-06", "aSentId": 43, "question": "Yeah.  Thats the amount that you have to pay out of pocket every year for healt", "qSentId": 42},{"answer": " Unfortunately, thats how it works.  You have to pay the deductible, pay a co-pa", "docId": "05-06", "aSentId": 44, "question": " So I paid all this money for an insurance policy, but I still have to pay more", "qSentId": 43},{"answer": "It says here that my policy covers 80%.  So I have to pay 20% of the medica", "docId": "05-06", "aSentId": 49, "question": " Unfortunately, thats how it works.  You have to pay the deductible, pay a co-pa", "qSentId": 48},{"answer": " Thats right.  It can be expensive just for that 20% too", "docId": "05-06", "aSentId": 53, "question": "It says here that my policy covers 80%.  So I have to pay 20% of the medica", "qSentId": 52},{"answer": " I didnt realize health care was so expensive here", "docId": "05-06", "aSentId": 54, "question": " Thats right.  It can be expensive just for that 20% too", "qSentId": 53},{"answer": " It is", "docId": "05-06", "aSentId": 55, "question": " I didnt realize health care was so expensive here", "qSentId": 54},{"answer": " So, can I see any doctor I want to", "docId": "05-06", "aSentId": 56, "question": " It is", "qSentId": 55},{"answer": " No, you have to choose a doctor thats in-network.  Otherwise, the insuranc", "docId": "05-06", "aSentId": 57, "question": " So, can I see any doctor I want to", "qSentId": 56},{"answer": " How do I find one thats in-network", "docId": "05-06", "aSentId": 61, "question": " No, you have to choose a doctor thats in-network.  Otherwise, the insuranc", "qSentId": 60},{"answer": " Theres probably a website listed on that brochure.  You can search online fo", "docId": "05-06", "aSentId": 62, "question": " How do I find one thats in-network", "qSentId": 61},{"answer": " OK.  So, once I find a doctor I can just go see him, and the fees will be covere", "docId": "05-06", "aSentId": 66, "question": " Theres probably a website listed on that brochure.  You can search online fo", "qSentId": 65},{"answer": " It depends.  Usually, the doctors office or hospital will file a claim for you to th", "docId": "05-06", "aSentId": 70, "question": " OK.  So, once I find a doctor I can just go see him, and the fees will be covere", "qSentId": 69},{"answer": " It sounds so complicated", "docId": "05-06", "aSentId": 76, "question": " It depends.  Usually, the doctors office or hospital will file a claim for you to th", "qSentId": 75},{"answer": " I know.  I can sit down with you and read through the brochure.  That way we ca", "docId": "05-06", "aSentId": 77, "question": " It sounds so complicated", "qSentId": 76},{"answer": " Thanks.  Id appreciate that", "docId": "05-06", "aSentId": 83, "question": " I know.  I can sit down with you and read through the brochure.  That way we ca", "qSentId": 82},{"answer": " No problem.  The health insurance system is confusing enough for Americans, le", "docId": "05-06", "aSentId": 84, "question": " Thanks.  Id appreciate that", "qSentId": 83},{"answer": " I just hope I dont get sick.  Maybe Ill never have to use it", "docId": "05-06", "aSentId": 88, "question": " No problem.  The health insurance system is confusing enough for Americans, le", "qSentId": 87},{"answer": " Hopefully not.  But its good that you do have insurance, just in case somethin", "docId": "05-06", "aSentId": 89, "question": " I just hope I dont get sick.  Maybe Ill never have to use it", "qSentId": 88},{"answer": " Yeah, I guess", "docId": "05-06", "aSentId": 93, "question": " Hopefully not.  But its good that you do have insurance, just in case somethin", "qSentId": 92}]
